Hello. I'm Mitch Treece.

I'm an innovative software engineer & leader, with a knack for UI/X design. I specialize in building consumer-facing mobile applications, as-well-as the SDK's & libraries that support them. With 10+ years of experience, I can turn things on their heads, think outside the box, and above all else - put usability and simplicity at the center of my development process.

Education

2013 | BS

COMPUTER SCIENCE

Central Washington University

2011 | AA

NATURAL SCIENCE

Green River Community College

Skills & Highlights

- Swift, Objective-C, C++, C#, Node.is, Vapor, & Go
- iOS, iPadOS, watchOS, tvOS, & Android platform knowledge
- Modern architecture using MVVM, DI, & reactive (Combine / Rx) frameworks
- Modern dependency management using SPM & Cocoapods
- CI automation (Github Actions, Xcode Server, Fastlane, & Jenkins)
- Experience leading & scaling engineering teams
- Startup, B2B, & M&A experience
- Coffee snob **Yes**, this is a skill =

Experience

2023 - PRESENT

ENGINEERING LEAD | CO-FOUNDER

WING | LOS ANGELES, CA

Lead a team of engineers across mobile, backend, & frontend web. Architected the Wing tech-stack, iOS application, & support libraries. Work with SLT on brand, design, investment, & marketing efforts.

2019 - 2023

MOBILE LEAD

AIRVET | LOS ANGELES, CA | APP STORE | PLAY STORE

Lead a team of mobile engineers across both iOS & Android platforms. Architected the Airvet parent & doctor iOS applications & support libraries. Worked closely with product, design, & SL teams for roadmap & product planning.

2018 - 2019

SR. IOS ENGINEER

AUTOGRAVITY | IRVINE, CA

Developed & maintained core & white-label applications, libraries, & tools. Managed iOS release automation & CI pipeline.

2016 - 2018

SR. IOS ENGINEER

TV TIME / WHIPCLIP | SANTA MONICA, CA | APP STORE | PLAY STORE

Developed & maintained the Whipclip iOS application, as well as the project's transition into TV Time; via company acquisition. Led the migration effort from Objective-C → 100% Swift. Worked alongside Product & Design teams for a complete re-branding & UI/X overhaul.

2015 - 2016

LEAD IOS ENGINEER

FUSION OF IDEAS | LAKE FOREST, CA

Lead a team of mobile engineers across both iOS & Android platforms. Developed & maintained iOS B2B applications and underlying frameworks for several high-profile clients.

2011 - 2015

IOS ENGINEER

SBCODERS | INDEPENDENT | SEATTLE, WA | LOS ANGELES, CA

DECK | AERO | DASH | PAGES+ | FANCY | TOUCHY

Created, developed, & maintained jailbroken iOS applications, packages, & libraries distributed via Cvdia.



E mitchtreece@me.com **P** 253.906.0972

Made with ♥ in Los Angeles, CA 😎

